right now we'll move on and talk about
another pocket which is the life
insurance space those stocks are trading
Under Pressure uh surbi is joining us
here uh with what's happening despite
decent set of numbers that these
companies reported should be
as we've been pointing out the life
insurance monthly data for the month of
March is extremely strong so the stock
prices are are giving us a different
picture all life insurance companies are
trending downwards in today's trading
session and a couple of reasons for that
could be one this growth is being driven
by the increase in the average ticket
size of policies and not by the number
of policies being sold and two this
accelerated growth could impact the
numbers for fy24 now as the growth will
be on a higher base now all brokerages
also have a similar view but they still
are positive on this life insurance
space HSBC says that they have cut down
their fy24 ape estimates by 600 pesos
points kotak says Q4 fi 23 was higher
than their estimates translating into a
higher base but they will wait for all
companies to report their numbers before
they revise their fy24 estimates MK
expects a flatish kind of ape growth for
fy24 and lastly investex says that the
budget proposals will impact the value
proposition in the high ticket segment
but according to their estimates it is
only 10 to 12 percent of the vnb for all
life insurance companies they're all
positive for the space but ape grows for
F5 24 Still Remains a concern
okay all right uh survey thanks very
much for that well